xmodgames.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy-Xmodgames

Your privacy is important to Xmodgames Team and we are committed to protecting your privacy. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

We DO NOT collect, store or use any personal information while you visit, download or upgrade our website or our products, excepting the personal information that you submit to us when you create a user account, send an error report or participate in online surveys and other activities.

Only for the following purposes that we may use personal information submitted by you: help us develop, deliver, and improve our products and services and supply higher quality service; manage online surveys and other activities you’ve participated in.

In the following circumstances, we may disclose your personal information according to your wish or regulations by law:

    (1)   Your prior permission;

    (2)   By the applicable law within or outside your country of residence, legal process, litigation requests;

    (3)   By requests from public and governmental authorities;

    (4)   To protect our legal rights and interests. 

 **NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Non-personal information is data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual, such as your CPN model, memory size, your phone IMEI number, phone model, install, uninstall, frequency of use, etc.

We may collect and use non-personal information in the following circumstances. To have a better understanding in user’s behavior, solve problems in products and services, improve our products, services and advertising, we may collect non-personal information such as the data of install, frequency of use, country, equipment and channel.

If non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

 **PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We take precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

When you use some products, services, or post your comments, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. Please take care when using these features.

 **OUR TEAMWIDE COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**

To make sure your personal information is secure; we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to all team members and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the team.

 **PRIVACY QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or data processing, please [contact us](http://www.xmodgames.com/contact/).

We may update Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.
